Good morning, Trap Stars. Views from Amanda Land goes live at 10 a.m. Eastern on YouTube,
Amanda Seals TV. Make sure you go over there and join us. Today, we have Tiago Avila of the
Freedom Flotilla, who is now organizing the Sumud Flotilla, which is going to have
many boats sailing to end the siege in Ghesa. We also have folks from Nodukdo for Korean
Community Development, an organization dedicated to not only getting the United States out of
Korea, but finally bringing Korea back together as one country. If you don't know about that 38th
Parallel, then make sure you join us. We also have leftist Leroy stopping in to put us on to what's
going down in D.C. and much more because there's so much more going on in this world and that's what
we do. We don't just give the news, we contextualize it over at YouTube, Amanda Seals TV. So join us and
wake up on the right side of history at 10 a.m.